♪Hey, you, you, you, why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes, even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you, why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts, my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again? That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you? That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along. Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you? The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out, "I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women" by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 5=
Boss, it's your day off.
What are you doing here?
Close the door. I want to show you something.
What is it?
I pulled this together from Shanlifang's materials.
Take a look.
The valuation of intangible assets isn't compliant.
The amortization treatment isn't compliant either.
They've done a lot to artificially inflate goodwill.
In the financial statements,
There are also obvious related party transactions.
And signs of deliberately inflating revenue and profits.
This is huge...
Such large-scale fraud,
And it's hidden this well.
Chairman Liao really went to great lengths.
Well, he's got professionals helping him.
I'm telling you, this has to be re-audited.
Boss,
To be honest, if you hadn't dug into it,
No one would've found it.
There's no reaction from Hejing.
Fang Yun and the others probably don't even know yet.
You're seriously underestimating her.
She's handled more projects than I have.
If I can spot these issues,
Do you really think she can't?
Then why hasn't she said anything?
At the very least, she should discuss how to deal with it with us.
The first person to bring this into the open
Becomes the one who offends Liao Jinshan.
She's not stupid.
Then what's her plan?
Let Shanlifang pass the review without a hitch?
If we all keep quiet,
And the regulator investigates later,
The moment they uncover a problem,
Neither she nor I will get away with it.
Helping someone break the law is destroying your own future.
The only solution is for none of us to hide.
We pressure Shanlifang together.
But Fang Yun is clearly pretending not to notice.
Because she's waiting for us
To expose the problem first.
We do the dirty work.
She takes the credit.
Got it?
That's shameless.
But we can't knowingly stay silent either.
If we do that,
Aren't we giving her exactly what she wants?
Let's leave it for now.
She's afraid of Liao Jinshan.
I'm not.
Keep digging.
By the way...
Uncle, wait for me.
I forgot a document.
Why do you need it now? Finish it tomorrow.
I can't.
Ms. Fang is already upset.
She said I have to give it to her tomorrow morning.
Otherwise, I won't be able
To stay on this project team.
She dares give you trouble?
Tell me. I'll stand up for you.
How?
She's Hejing's star performer.
She's not like Qian Fei,
Who can be laid off so easily.
Just wait in the car for a bit.
I'll be quick.
All right. Hurry up.
Okay.
(Shanghai World Financial Center)
Didn't you already leave the company?
Why are you still here?
I wanted to know for sure why I was laid off.
That's right. You saw it yourself.
Mr. Kong is my uncle.
You think you were laid off because of my uncle?
Wasn't I?
Your professional skills are strong.
But after all these years at the company,
You still don't know what you want.
If the two of us competed fairly,
I'd stay and you'd be the one laid off.
That's perfectly normal.
Whether Mr. Kong is my uncle
Has very little to do with it.
But you still can't see that.
I know why you're here.
To see Ms. Fang.
And ask her for a job.
Oh? Can't stay in your comfort zone anymore?
Take a look at yourself.
Why would she give you a job?
Give it up.
(Why would Ms. Fang give me a chance?)
(Yeah. Why would she?)
(Xinyao was right.)
(She works harder than I do.)
(And she's far more clear-headed.)
Stop yelling. It's me. It's me.
It's me. Can you stop screaming now?
You nearly scared me to death.
Who's scaring who? Looking like that!
Like a ghost.
This is Gui Lili's face mask.
It felt like a waste to throw it away, so I used it.
This mask is actually pretty nice.
What's going on with the house?
How would I know? I should be asking you.
The power suddenly went out. It's dark in here.
Everything outside is fine.
What's going on inside?
You didn't use some high power appliance, did you?
I...
I know.
Could it be the new oven I bought?
You bought an oven?
It's huge.
Where is it?
Here.
Look how big it is.
It's huge.
Who told you to buy an oven?
What do you want to do?
To heat pizza.
Can't you use the microwave?
The texture isn't the same.
I don't allow it.
You don't allow it?
I thought since I paid for it, you could use it, too.
I figured you'd be happy about it.
This isn't about the money.
It's about the electrical safety risks
Caused by your lack of common sense.
Then... Then does that mean the dishwasher's out, too?
You bought a dishwasher, too?
Yeah. Then neither of us would have to wash dishes anymore.
Wouldn't that be great?
Come on. Look at this kitchen.
Where exactly would a dishwasher fit?
I guess there really isn't any space.
Then what do we do?
Why don't we just renovate the kitchen?
Wouldn't that solve it?
It's only a couple of dishes.
Washing them takes less than a minute.
But a dishwasher spins and spins
For two whole hours, buzzing the entire time.
What's wrong with that?
Who cares if it's noisy?
Just replace your bedroom door
With a soundproof one.
Why don't you just tear the whole house down and rebuild it?
Where are you going?
To fix it.
Not everyone is like you,
Content to stumble around in the dark.
That's it?
The breaker tripped.
If this happens again,
Just flip the switch back up.
It's pretty late. Who is it?
Who is it?
The electrician.
The electrician?
Hello.
Hello. Your power went out, right?
Yes, but it's fixed now. The breaker tripped.
Even if nothing needed fixing,
There's still a service call fee.
A service call?
You called him?
I didn't know it only needed a flip of the switch.
So how much is the fee?
Two hundred.
This is an emergency late-night call.
Of course there's an extra charge.
That's fair.
Definitely.
Here. I'll scan you. Or you scan me.
You can scan me.
Okay.
Two hundred.
All right. Thanks for coming out.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
You're amazing.
Why couldn't you just give the money to me?
I didn't know you knew how to fix it.
And I didn't know when you'd be home.
Couldn't you just look it up online?
There'd be tens of thousands of results online.
The time it'd take me to figure it out,
I could've made several times that amount.
If money can solve a problem,
Don't waste time doing it yourself.
Landlady, let me tell you.
Your time is worth more than money.
Stop wasting it.
What's wrong?
Did I say something wrong?
No.
It's just that no one's ever told me
My time was worth more than money.
So when I think about
All that valuable time I wasted
On people who didn't deserve it,
It really makes me angry.
As long as you're not mad at me.
Look.
With me around, it's great, right?
The longer we live together, the more you'll realize
There's a lot you can learn from me.
So?
If you want to become my apprentice,
I'm still willing to take you on.
Seriously?
How do you have the nerve to say that?
You just made a fool of yourself,
And wasted 200 yuan for nothing.
What do I learn from you? How to waste money?
Waste money?
It's called a way of life.
You wouldn't understand.
Fine. Don't learn.
You're the one who should be learning. Come with me.
Hurry up.
The main gas shutoff.
It's up here.
This is the main gas valve.
If you're leaving for a long time,
Make sure you turn it off. It's dangerous.
And when you cook,
You know how to turn it on, right?
I don't cook.
You'll need it to boil water.
I only drink bottled water.
Anyway,
If you ever need to use it,
Make sure to turn it off afterward.
I didn't realize there were so many shutoffs.
Seriously, how did you survive before?
Where I used to live, there was a twenty-four-hour concierge.
One phone call solved everything.
Seriously? That's such a waste of money.
Why not just learn it yourself?
Now I finally know why you never save any money.
Why?
Just like you said,
Your time is bought with money.
So now you're broke and have too much free time.
Your arguing skills are improving.
Let me tell you something, Landlady.
Don't think
Owning an apartment makes you rich.
Take the value of this apartment,
Subtract depreciation, taxes, fees and maintenance costs,
Then add your mortgage, money borrowed from friends and family,
And thirty years of future interest payments.
Do the math.
What else?
The lost returns from cash investments,
All the favors you owe, the time and energy you've spent,
And the risk of losing your job and defaulting.
You're not much richer than I am. I mean it.
With all that financial talk...
You used to work in investment banking.
How can you not figure out a simple calculation like that?
I think it's time I introduced you to a plastic surgeon.
What do you mean?
A little work here and here.
What? Get surgery and I won't have to pay my mortgage?
Make your eyes a little bigger.
Broaden your horizons a little.
Instead of obsessing over things like
Apartments, breakers, and shutoffs all day.
Li Yifei.
Stop talking down to me.
Get your own life in order first.
You don't even know basic life skills.
How did your mom raise you?
My mom
Passed away a long time ago.
Um...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Just like you,
I lost my mom at a young age, too.
So...
I know exactly
How you feel.
Why are we talking about this?
Oh, right.
You got a package today.
I left it in your room.
Thanks.
(Time)
(Fei, I was looking through some old photos the other day.)
(I picked out a few and sent them to you.)
(You're about to have a home of your own.)
(Since your parents can't be there with you,)
(let these photos keep you company instead.)
(Every time we talk on the phone,)
(you always tell me how well you're doing.)
(Ms. He and I are happy to hear that.)
(But I also know)
(you only share the good news and keep the worries to yourself.)
(Life can't always be smooth sailing.)
(There will always be difficult times.)
(Don't worry about making me worry.)
(The good and the bad,)
(you can tell me about all of it.)
(Even after you get married,)
(and become someone's wife,)
(and someone's mother,)
(you'll always be my dearest daughter first.)
(Whenever you miss home, come back.)
(Whenever you need someone to talk to, call me.)
(I will always be here for you.)
(Dad)
Fei?
Hi, Dad.
I got the photos and the letter.
Fei.
You've been crying?
No, I haven't.
Really, I'm fine.
I know.
It's not easy trying to build a life in a big city.
When you're tired, come home and rest.
You were about to get married anyway.
Ms. He and I
Were hoping you'd stay a few extra days.
And we'd get a chance to talk to Ruohai, too.
There's no need, Dad.
We broke up.
You broke up?
You... broke up?
What happened, Fei?
Did he hurt you?
No. He didn't.
And I wasn't wronged in any way.
It's just...
We had different plans
For the future.
We couldn't keep going.
How is that possible?
You've been together for so many years.
How could you only discover those problems
Right before getting married?
Fei.
You're not telling me the whole truth.
That is the truth, Dad.
Fei.
Whatever decision you make,
Dad supports you.
I know.
Okay, Dad. I'll hang up now.
Get some sleep.
♪What matters to me is what you need♪
♪No more, no less. I only hope I can give it to you♪
♪What I treasure is what I have♪
♪Bit by bit, I only hope you're there with me♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks lighting up the midnight sky♪
♪Truths, lies, and words said for appearances♪
♪Leaving me feeling like I'm walking on air♪
♪Harsh words, lies, and words I can't make sense of♪
♪All dressed up in hollow splendor♪
♪Dreams, madness, and the words in my heart♪
♪Beneath this burning gaze♪
♪What I dream of is being with you♪
♪Taking it slow, hand in hand♪
♪What I long for is something lasting♪
♪Day after day, simply holding you close♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks lighting up the midnight sky♪
♪Truths, lies, and words said for appearances♪
♪Leaving me feeling like I'm walking on air♪
♪Harsh words, lies, and words I can't make sense of♪
♪All dressed up in hollow splendor♪
♪Dreams, madness, and the words in my heart♪
♪Beneath this burning gaze♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks lighting up the midnight sky♪
♪Dreams, madness, and the words in my heart♪
Don't you not know how to boil water?
It's not that I can't.
It's that there's no need to.
When the need arises,
I'm capable of just about anything.
One man worth two.
Give me a break.
You only made a cup of cocoa.
Listen to yourself. You sound like an Olympic champion.
It's not about the cocoa.
It's about helping someone when they need it most.
Remember.
You owe me one now.
I owe you?
Why? I bought the cocoa powder.
You just mixed it.
We're even.
You really know how to keep score.
I worked in investment banking, after all.
Even if I'm unemployed now...
At least you know what you're about.
Life is one long investment in yourself.
Time and energy
Are our capital.
We...
All right.
I'm not in the mood for a lecture today.
I have research reports to work on.
You don't even have a job. Why are you writing research reports?
What's with the attitude?
Thanks.
Making cocoa is an investment in yourself now.
(Li Yifei is right.)
(Life is a wholehearted investment in yourself.)
(I used to think)
(that building a stable family)
(was a one-time investment with guaranteed returns.)
(Important Notice) (But investment and risk)
(always come together.)
(Even banks can fail.)
(What in this world comes with guaranteed returns?)
(Putting your future into love)
(is like taking a gamble with everything you have.)
(Information Technology Department)
This is the result of your work?
At this morning's meeting,
They said our department's efficiency has dropped lately,
And mistakes are everywhere, affecting the work of the business division.
How do you make mistakes with templated business analysis data?
How do you lose files for reporting and management?
And for the simplest system maintenance jobs,
How is no one available?
Seriously.
Can you all pull yourselves together and make my life easier?
Ms. He Li,
We've really been trying.
We've all been working overtime lately.
What's the point of overtime if the data is still wrong?
Get yourselves together.
Review your own work,
And submit a report to me.
And all of those need to be redone.
(Information Technology Department)
Look how angry He Li is.
Qian Fei used to handle all those files.
Now that she's gone,
The whole back end department is a mess.
Now that you mention it,
I kind of miss her, too.
Yeah. She was really capable.
How was she the one who got laid off?
You're so loud. Are you going to let anyone sleep?
You should get up too.
A regular schedule is good for your health.
A regular schedule, my foot.
You stay up all night and won't let anyone sleep during the day.
What's gotten into you?
What kind of door is this? No soundproofing at all.
Landlady, this early in the morning...
♪Hey, you, you, you, why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes♪
♪Even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite raindrops in spring♪
♪Or a kitten on a lazy afternoon♪
♪Hey♪
♪Why is it always you? The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out, "I like you. I only like you."♪
I'm heading out.
Bye.
This woman...
She sure knows how to make an impression.
She does seem a little different today.
Jingjing.
You're looking good today.
Looks like you've already...
Hang on a second.
Hello?
Yes, that display board has to be redone.
You can't finish it?
Then work overtime and redo it.
It can't be used now.
The text is printed backwards.
I don't care.
Whatever he wants, he can't ruin my reputation.
Handle it for now.
And I'm having lunch right now.
No calls for the next half hour.
Bye.
You're so busy. Maybe you should head back.
It's fine.
I need a breather, too.
If I'd known you were this busy,
I wouldn't have asked you out today.
This is nothing.
I even got five hours of sleep last night.
When things really get busy,
I won't even get to see my pillow.
You mentioned a research report on the phone.
You wanted me to take a look?
Maybe let's forget it today and do it next time.
I've got time for this.
Come on. Let me see it.
A research report on Shanlifang?
I want to go back to Hejing.
Can you look at this report
And tell me if it'll impress Ms. Fang?
Go back to Hejing, join Fang Yun's project team,
And work on Shanlifang's IPO.
Do you think it's possible?
Of course it's possible.
With your ability,
There's no problem at all.
So?
I think it's very well written.
Then give me some suggestions.
I think you should get a professional to look at it.
A professional?
The only people I know are my former colleagues.
It wouldn't be appropriate to ask them now.
Why ask former colleagues?
You're overlooking the obvious.
What could be more obvious than that?
Your place. That tenant of yours.
Doesn't he work in investment banking too?
You mean Li Yifei?
He loafs around all day.
What useful advice could he give?
Loafs around?
Didn't Dang Yu tell you he's a project team leader?
That's the same level as Fang Yun.
He was only put there to make up the numbers.
Even so,
He knows more than a back end analyst like you.
That's true.
That actually makes sense.
But look at how smug he is every day.
If I go ask him for advice now,
His ego will shoot through the roof.
You still care about that?
A true winner knows when to bend and when to stand tall.
Slow down.
Don't scrape the floor.
Right. Lift it up.
Okay.
Watch the door frame above. Careful.
Li Yifei, what are you doing?
You're back.
Changing the door.
Don't worry. I'm paying for it.
Don't worry about it.
I don't need to worry about it?
This is my house.
Did I ever tell you to replace the door?
Come on, isn't it in the lease?
I have the right to make changes
To my room for convenience.
This door is part of my room, isn't it?
You have no right to interfere.
The lease says so?
Check it yourself if you don't believe me.
What was so inconvenient
About the old door?
That old thing wasn't soundproof.
You didn't buy a dishwasher, did you?
I'm telling you, Li Yifei.
I just bought these cabinets.
If you dare...
Relax.
I returned the dishwasher.
You're the one using the kitchen anyway.
Why would I spend money renovating it?
Then why are you replacing the door?
How many times do I have to tell you? It's not soundproof.
I can hear you brushing your teeth every morning.
I can hear you walking around.
I can hear your phone calls.
The washing machine.
The refrigerator.
I can even hear you grinding your teeth at night.
It's affecting my sleep, okay?
I don't grind my teeth.
Fine. But what if I did?
Anyway,
This door benefits both of us.
The whole world becomes quieter.
Neither of us will bother the other.
Besides, doesn't it match
The style of your place?
Looks great.
You should be thanking me.
It's okay. No need to thank me too much.
Who said I was thanking you?
Sir,
Please be careful during installation.
I've already told them.
Like I need you to remind me.
Right, be careful.
Don't scratch or bump anything.
The landlady bites, trust me.
Li Yifei and that mouth of his.
One sentence and he can drive you crazy.
How am I supposed to ask him for help now?
This event wrapped up early,
But that doesn't mean we can slack off.
This materials list needs to be sorted by category,
And then sent to me as soon as possible.
Bye.
Lu Ze.
(Lu Ze, I never expected)
(that you're the same kind of person as Wang Ruohai.)
(You're even better at hiding it than he is.)
You look different today.
More energetic, right?
I don't look as down as before.
Right?
Honey.
I've been doing some serious thinking.
I've really neglected you lately.
So I've decided
To make it up to you
While work isn't too busy.
And how are you going to make it up to me?
It's been a long time since we've...
So that's what you're into.
Whatever you like, sweetheart.
Whatever I like?
Whatever I like...
Honey! Ouch!
That hurts, sweetheart.
Ouch!
No.
Oh, sweetheart.
Don't call me sweetheart.
Wait. Why are you getting angry?
You're asking why I'm angry?
Don't tell me you have no idea.
What have you been up to all day?
Who did you meet today?
If you lie to me about even one word,
We're breaking up right now.
Fine.
Then let me ask you.
Why did you come home so early today?
I finished work.
And the first thing you did was take a shower.
Because I missed you so much. I couldn't help myself.
And you even did the laundry.
I was helping with the housework.
Fine.
Then what about the mud on your shoes?
There's not even a park near your office.
How did your shoes get so muddy?
There could be mud on the roads in the neighborhood.
That's perfectly normal.
I'm telling you, you're acting very strange today.
And this?
Who did you buy this for?
Fine.
I'll explain.
Here's what happened.
After the forum,
Things weren't so busy at work anymore.
So,
I thought it was time to move our plans forward.
And then,
You bought this ring?
That's right.
I even planned a special proposal.
So I went out early this morning to rehearse it.
Otherwise, why would there be mud on my shoes?
Really?
Really.
Why...
Why would I lie about something like this?
Look.
I even recorded videos.
Early this morning.
Marry...
Mom.
Marry Mom.
No.
I was still rehearsing.
Of course there were going to be a few mistakes.
Ugh, you're so annoying. You figured it out.
There goes the surprise.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I misjudged you.
Since you've already found out,
I might as well propose now.
Be serious. Stand up.
Be serious.
Wait.
You call this serious?
I am serious.
Yao Jingjing.
Even though the proposal isn't fully prepared,
My heart is.
Will you marry me?
♪I really miss you, miss you so much♪
♪My heart keeps racing♪
♪Keeping time with every breath♪
♪Tuned to the rhythm of missing you♪
I will.
♪You're the only one in the world♪
♪Living in my heart♪
♪I really miss you, miss you so much♪
♪My heart keeps racing♪
♪Keeping time with every breath♪
♪Tuned to the rhythm of missing you♪
So it goes on this finger.
Honey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
♪Living in my heart♪
Let's go.
Take care of some important business.
What do you want to do?
Um...
Have you had dinner yet?
If you don't mind,
Why don't we eat together?
You're treating me to dinner?
Come on, let's go.
Seriously?
Seriously. Let's go.
Hold on.
Inviting me to dinner out of nowhere?
People don't do favors
For no reason.
If you don't want to eat, that's fine.
I won't force you.
Why not?
Why wouldn't I eat?
Free food is free food.
I'm in.
But let me make one thing clear.
I have a slight germ issue.
I don't like people
Picking from the same plate with me.
Got it. Individual servings. Sounds good.
Smart.
Very smart.
Here.
I remember you like eggplant, right?
Take some more.
Then I will.
I won't hold back.
Don't. Seriously, don't.
Not bad. Tastes great.
See?
Landlady,
I've got to say,
You've got talent.
You could be a chef. Seriously.
Why aren't you eating? Go ahead.
Don't sit there smiling at me. You're creeping me out.
You're overthinking it. You're my tenant.
We should keep a good relationship.
It's only right for me
To treat you to a meal now and then.
Don't read too much into it.
That's true.
Eat up before it gets cold.
Delicious.
But let me be clear up front.
I'm absolutely not washing dishes.
A gentleman uses his mouth, not his hands.
I'm only here to eat.
How could I make you wash dishes?
This meal is completely my treat.
Just enjoy it.
All right.
If you're eating but not washing dishes,
Doesn't that mean you owe me a favor?
See?
I knew it. You had an ulterior motive.
Go on.
Go on. What's the catch?
Well, you know,
I'm a very straightforward person.
The only reason I'm doing this
Is that you left me no choice.
What do you mean?
=Love Has Fireworks= (Next Episode Preview)
I've realized that you're pretty interesting sometimes.
Most girls after a breakup
Cry and make a scene.
But you act as if nothing happened.
That person
Was the biggest flaw in my life plan.
Now that it's fixed,
He's no longer needed.
Ms. Fang.
This is the research report I prepared on Shanlifang.
I want to know where exactly I fell short.
A person who doesn't know how to cherish
Will never be truly valuable.
Do you understand?
♪There's no need to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords with the wind♪
♪There's no need to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone, yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly like the stars and the moon on high♪